ALI HADADI THE CODER WHO DESIGNS



PERSONAL INFO

WEBSITE:

infamousrocket.com

EMAIL:

fly@infamousrocket.com

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/alihadadi

DATE OF BIRTH:

January 28, 1999

PLACE OF BIRTH:

Iran

LANGUAGES

PERSIAN:

ENGLISH:

GERMAN:

∅ -•>

^

BEGINNER

HOBBIES

WORKOUT - CODE - DESIGN CARDS - CHESS - SING - COOK MUSIC - VIDEO GAMES - READ WRITE - MEDITATE - HELP

SPREAD POSITIVITY - LEARN

Dedicated web developer with 5 years of experience sharing identical affections in designing, having integrated innovation and creativity aligned with ideal quality. Interested on fully responsive and interactive modules & layouts resulting in 40% more flexible outcomes.

EXPERIENCE

2018-04- Lead front-end developer & UI/UX designer 2019-06 Vestaak. Tehran

- Introduced innovative and modernized ideas increasing client's recognition of influential detail while ensuring appealing visual appearance.
- Redesigned layouts in a more practical approach and implemented simplified algorithms.
- Participated on events and tasks refining presented insights, improved revisions and prioritized objectives.
- Mentored front-end trainees inspiring them to be more.

In conclusion:

- Transformed company's image on front-end contracts.
- Enhanced overall speed and smoothness of client-side interactions by 30%.
- Conceptualized and initiated inaccessible formats.

2015-08- Web developer & digital designer PRESENT Freelancer

- Systemized dull assignments by centralizing objectoriented programming.
- Initiated user-friendly interactions by mastering web animation techniques.
- Boosted both abilities to create simple and chaotic layouts and patterns.
- Counselled entrepreneurs on promoting their businesses.
- Reinforced project-management and punctuality skills.
- Collaborated with experts from several IT divisions.
- Strengthened data collecting and research abilities.
- Improved Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Techniques.
- Operated Content Management Systems (CMS).
- Modified source code management methods by using Version Control Systems (VCS) such as Git.

EDUCATION

2013-06- High School Diploma

2017-06 Dr. Mahmoud Afshar High School of Math Tehran, Tehran

CERTIFICATES

Tehran Institute of Technology

2015-08 Dynamic website makeover

2015-03 JQuery & Ajax

2015-01 JavaScript, Methodology

2014-11 Cascading Style Sheets

2014-09 Web Design Foundation

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Programmer		Web designer
HTML	MASTER \(ILLUSTRATORMASTER \(\sqrt{\sqrt{MASTER}} \)
CSS	MASTER	PHOTOSHOPMASTER \(
JS	MASTER	Frameworks
PHP	SKILLED	
MYSQL	SKILLED \(JQuery Bootstrap SemanticUI GSAF